Herm is a fully automated digital employee that works
directly on your computer
and can operate 24/7.  And the
more you work with it, the more
it will understand you, the smarter it will become,
and it will have a very
interesting ability: the ability to create its own
skills and abilities through the
process of working with you.  And hello
everyone, I'm Phan Ong Giang.  This will
be a comprehensive and complete overview video about
Hent.  I will guide you
step-by-step on how to set up Herration
and run it on your VPS with just a few
clicks, without needing to know a
single line of code.  And I will also guide
you on how to connect Telegram so
you can send commands to
the Hermit agent via
your phone, how to turn
your work process into
a skill, and how to create a chron
job so that the Hermit agent
can work according to your schedule.
It can operate on an hourly, daily,
or weekly basis, and there are ways for you to
track costs and also
how you can choose or change
models to suit different tasks
when using this Herm A.  And
I will also compare it with its competitor,
OpenClaw, to see
what advantages and disadvantages each AI has and which
AI agent would be suitable for your work
.  Now, let's begin with
what a Hermit agent is.  Hermate agent is
an AI agent with open language code.  And because it's in
open language, you can download
and use it for free.  If
you've ever watched videos,
read content, or are familiar with
Open Claw, you'll know that
Open Claw works as one
of your variables.  It can do
everything, and this agent is no
different.  However, agents have a
really cool feature: they have the ability to
evolve on their own.  This means that the more you
use it, the better it understands you, the
smarter it becomes, and it can run continuously
on your system—
24/7. Even when your computer is
turned off, this server can still
receive requests, respond to information, and
work for you
according to your schedule,
without you needing to turn on your computer.  And this
is the great thing about
using it on a VPS virtual server
.  And secondly, it has the ability to
remember how you work.  When you
input any information and
the longer and more frequently you work with it,
the more it will remember
your habits, preferences, and
information.  And another extremely cool feature,
and also a
trademark of Hent, is its
ability to automatically create skills. When
you're doing a
complex task, Hent
will automatically package a
skill or ability so that when
you do that task again later,
it will automatically call that skill.
And this will save you
a lot of time and
money.  Because
these already have a
well-structured process, there's no need to figure things out on
your own anymore.  Now, let's compare
Open Claw with Herent to see their
advantages and disadvantages, and which one is
right for
us.  First, I'll talk about the
design philosophy.  You understand the design philosophy
behind these two devices, and
what they focus on.  For those of
you familiar with Open Claw, you
'll know that it boasts an
incredibly powerful skill ecosystem
.  With over 50,000 skill ivory now, that's
probably more than enough.  As for Hion,
it focuses on the idea
that the learning loop is like a
circle, you know.  This means that when you
do a job, you'll
repeatedly work, think,
check, and then improve the process.
This will help
you solve problems faster
and more cost-effectively.  So, it's
like, once you're used to it,
you can do things faster and
more cost-effectively.  However,
in my opinion, these two strengths of the two AIs are also
their weaknesses.  For example, Open
Claw has a huge ecosystem
with 50,000 skills,
most of which are
developed by the community, so it has
its own security issues
.  Similarly, Hion
doesn't have a huge inventory like Open Claw,
but it requires learning gradually, so
its self-learning process takes longer
than downloading a skill
.  It is because of those two points that
we will have this problem revealed on the surface.
The problem is that with OpenClaw,
their skill library is so vast, and you don't
know if the
communities or individuals
who created those skills have included
any malicious code within those skill files
.  The
advice here is that you should only install
skills from reliable sources
and always update to the
latest versions.  Herent, on the other hand, has
fewer security vulnerabilities
compared to Open Claw because it doesn't have a
skill library like Open Claw
does.  However, everything has
its own security issues, you
know.  You still need to be cautious and
keep updating to
the latest versions to ensure
safety.  So, whether you should choose an
open claw or not depends
on your preferences, desires, and
the nature of your work
.  Choose Hion if you
want a character that can
learn automatically over time, create its own
skills, and you don't want to
install skills that you're worried about
regarding security issues.  And you want
a British child who gets smarter the more they work
.  You have tasks that
you repeat many times.
If you don't have much
variety in your work,
Homation is a reasonable choice
because it can automatically create
skills to repeat
your tasks, thereby increasing your work speed
and saving you costs
.  As for you, open claw is
very diverse, and you can't
wait for these creatures to learn,
become smarter, and develop
skills on their own—that would be time-consuming. If
you need a set of
skills to handle a particular task,
then open claw is a good
choice for you.  Now, let's
move on to three ways
you can run this action.
First, you can install
this directly on your computer
.  Your laptop.  And
secondly, you can install it on a
separate PC.  That could be a
desktop PC, a mini PC,
or some kind of old computer.  a
computer that you guys use specifically for
this Her.  And the third method, in my opinion,
is still the best: the
VPS method.  And why did I choose to
run this agent on a VPS
or Open Claw?  I also run it on a
VPS.  This is why, if you run
Herm Agent on your laptop,
when you shut down your computer, the Herm
Agent will also shut down and
will stop working for you.  And the
second problem is that running it on
your laptop is unsafe
because your laptop
contains your information and
data, so there's a high chance
this malware will access
your documents and information.  It will
compromise the security of your private information
.  The second option is to install it
on a separate PC.  For example, a
mini PC or a
dedicated computer for this Hag would
work.  However, the drawback
of this method is that you need a
computer with very high specifications
.  Very high specifications.  Secondly,
you need a
substantial budget to invest in a PC like
this.  And thirdly, you also need to
keep the machine running continuously for this Hion to
work 24/7 for you.  As
for VPS, here we'll be using a VPS
from Hostinger, a
very popular VPS provider.  With a VPS,
it's always online.  This means that even if
you turn off your computer or go to sleep,
your Her device can still continue
working.  Alternatively, when you're out and about,
you can simply send messages via Telegram, and even
with your computer turned off,
your Hion device will continue working
for you.  Ha, this is exactly the
point I think is that
using AI on a VPS is
safer.  That means it won't
touch any of
your information or data on your computer
.  Another advantage is the good price;
you don't need to build a
PC costing tens of millions of VND or a
high-performance computer right away. You can
pay monthly.  And
in fact, for only about 200,000 VND a
month, you can get a
great VBS service.  Okay, so that
's some information I wanted to share about the
action and also the reasons why you
should use Hermion on a
virtual server (VPS) so that your agent
runs more securely and can run
24/7, always online to work for you.
Now I will guide you on
how to set up Hermit Agent on a
VPS, and I will be using a VPS on
Hostinger.  This is a
very reputable and popular supplier.  And
anyone who knows about websites, SEO,
domains, etc., will almost certainly know
about Hostinger, which is very popular
.  First, please
access this page so you can run
the Hion application on your
Hostinger VPS.  The link that allows
you to directly access
this page will be in the description
of each video.  If you click on it,
it will take you directly to this page.
Next, I'll click on the "Select
Package" section here, and it will scroll down to the section
where you can choose individual packages.  Here, I'll be
using the KVM2 package.  This
package is the most suitable for anyone who
does
typical office work.  For those of you who do
more complex work or
work multiple jobs simultaneously,
I encourage you to upgrade to
higher-tier packages.  Then here
I will click on the KVM2 package and then
click on select package.  Here, they will
default to this 24-month package.
With the 24-month package, you'll get the
cheapest price when divided among the parties involved.
If you find that too long, you
can choose the 12-month package here.
And when you register through the
link I've put in the
video description, you'll get
this discount.  And in addition, I'll have
an extra discount code for you guys
.  Click here for the discount code
and enter the code:
Phan Dong Giang.  When you
enter the discount code Phan Dong Giang,
you will get an additional 10% discount
.  Okay.  Before you proceed with
payment, here's some information
you need to be aware of.  Here, it will have
something quite interesting: AI (
artificial intelligence) ready for use.  This means that when
you select this option,
you don't need to enter the API key to
use the Her tool
.  Next, there's
another important feature here: the automatic
daily backup function.  This is an
important option for anyone
planning to use
AI agents like these long-term.
Your VPS will automatically back up its data for
you every day.  For example, you might do
something wrong, or you might install
something incorrectly, mistakenly, or something like
that.  So here you'll find places
where you can restore
previous versions, which will help keep
your VPS, your computer, or
your data
safer.  Next, you
need to choose the location of the main machine;
you can leave it as default here.  Okay,
here's another great thing:
you'll get a free 1-year KVT (Knowledge Transfer Token) for your region
when you register here
!  That's fantastic.  And here's something
I want to point out: you can
only get the discount and
enter this discount code if
you choose a package of 12 months or more
.  Now I'll click "
Continue" to proceed with payment.  Please
register for an account.  If you haven't already
registered a Hostinger account,
I'll register one using my
Google account here.  After you have
successfully logged in, please fill in your
payment information and make your
payment here.  Okay.  After you
successfully register, you will see an
interface like this.  So,
the
interface might look a little different while you're watching this video.
But rest assured, the
core principles, the important things,
will remain the same.  Then it
will take you to a page where you can
unlock this Hermet agent, and it will
include the admin username and
password.  And
this password section, you'll
see it like this when you click the button, then copy and
paste it in a safe place because this
is the password you'll use to
access your agent
.  And here I have a part called the
Nesus IP key.  I have this API key here
because the account and package
I registered for included the
Nesus API Key.  But later I
will also show you how to
install an IPI key from a
different provider.
Then click on Deploy here.
And now, please wait a moment for
it to deploy your agent
here.  Okay, so after about 1 to 2
minutes, my agent
has been successfully installed and is running
on my Hostinger VPS.
You'll see that everything is very
simple, right?  With just a few clicks,
I successfully installed it.  So
this is the Hostinger interface,
guys.  So now I'll need to go
into this Hion device to set
it up further.  Now,
click on the word "terminal" here.  Then
an interface like this will appear
.  Some of you might be
a little hesitant because the interface looks
too much like programming, too much like code,
and not very user-friendly, but don't
worry, it's okay.  It's very simple, guys,
and you don't need to type a single line of
code.  You just need to copy and
paste it, guys.  Now, here
you should click on the
blinking part.
Please click here.  Then,
please access the document link
that I've included in the
video description.  This document is a
compilation of commands that you
just need to copy and paste to successfully set up
your agent.
First, copy
the first command here,
then paste it into this field.  So,
there will be four X's here,
please delete these four X's for me.
Delete it.  And then please go back to the
Hostinger page.  And please
copy these four words for me.
Then, come here,
right-click, paste the text, and press Enter
.  Next, please
return to this document page.
Please copy this rule for me
.  Copy this.  And I'm back here.  And now
I'll continue pasting it on, guys.
You just need to copy and paste it.
Next, come back here and copy
the command 'H setup' from here.  Copy
this over here.  And please stick it back in place
for me.  Press Enter again.  Then
it will ask you how you want to set up
this Hermage.
It will have three options: the
first is quick setup, the second is
full setup.  So here, I won't choose
the quick setup option because
that option forces you to
use the services of
this NOS portal.  However, here I will choose
the second option, which is the full setup.
With this full setup, you are
free to choose the models and
suppliers according to
your preferences.  Then, all you have to do is
press enter, and it will show all the
providers.  The providers are the
companies that supply AI to
you.  So, with my account,
it automatically selects the AI ​​section
here.  Because the package I bought
already included this, guys.  So
we can use this AI without
needing an ABI or
other vendors.  However, here I will guide
you on how to choose a
supplier that meets your needs
.  And here I'll choose a
chewing gum that's very popular and widely
used.  So here I'll choose
Open Router.  To
adjust these buttons, you
should press the up and down buttons like this
.  Next, select "Open
Router" here and press enter
.  Next, it will show
you a page and it will ask
you to enter an
Open Router API key.  So where do I get
the Open Router API key now?  So,
this is the Open Router interface.
For those who don't know
what Open Router is, or
what its APIK is, Open
Router is an intermediary unit
that connects leading AI models
out there. Those models have
a lot of features, right?  So instead of having to
connect to
multiple different AIs.  For example,
AI from Claw,
Chat, Crop, Dipsit, and so on.  And
you have to connect each of the
new grandfather's ABY 1 codes.  With the operator, you
just need to connect to the correct operator IP address,
and it will automatically connect
you to many different AI models
.  Now that you understand
the role of the AP/OPer here,
let's register an
account.  The link
to register for Open Router
will be in the description of this
video.  Then I'll click on the "
sign up" button here.  Here, you can
register an account; I'll
quickly register using Google here.
After successfully registering, you
need to deposit money before you can
use the IBA key for Open Router
.  Here, we'll go to the section
that says "credits."  I'll add the credit
here later.  Here I will enter my name,
my location, and my
address.  Then, please enter
your payment information here and
save it.  Next, please enter
the amount you wish to
pay here.  For those of you who are new here,
I recommend that you
only deposit around 5 to 10 dollars.
Here, I'll just enter about 5 dollars.
Then I'll click "Pay" here.
So, my account has
now been credited with $5 like this,
guys.  It's very simple, right?
Now I'm going to create an API key.
Here, you click on the section that says API
key.  Here, you select "new key" and
then you should give
your API key a name.  I'll
reset the information here.  Here you can
set a spending limit for
yourself.  So, if you
want to control your expenses,
you should put
your numbers here.  For example, here
I want it to not cost more than $20
.  And here's the part about when it will reset
.  Do you want it to reset daily,
weekly, or monthly?
So here I'll leave it as "by month".  And
here, you can choose when you want it to expire
; you can add that option
here.  In general, this is a way for
you to control
your expenses.  If you don't want it to
exceed a certain amount,
please set it here.  Then, here
I will click "create".  Then, here it
will show you an ab key
.  And please copy this IP key
and paste it into a safe place.  Because when
you turn this off, it won't show up again
.  And secondly,
this is a very important piece of code.  If
others knew your IP address,
they could generally say they could
misuse your money.  So you should
copy and hide this API key carefully.
Now, let's go back to the
terminal page we were on earlier.  And please paste
your API key here.  Please
stick it in the area with the blue square box
.  Right-click here.  Press paste
.  Then press enter.  Then
it will display a list of
current AI models.  So here it
includes the latest and
most powerful AI models currently available.  For example,
Claw Fable 5, the
most powerful AI model currently available, is already here,
guys.  However, you
'll find that the most powerful models
here, especially the American AI models, are
very expensive.  Look at
the input and output sections
here; you'll find some
affordable but very smart models
.  Especially those coming from
Chinese guys.  Here are some examples,
like these dipsit gentlemen.  So, Dipsit
V4 Pro is very powerful, but look at the price – it's
very cheap compared to these other brands.
So, you should start by choosing the
cheaper models first.  Later in the
video, I'll
show you how to change the model.  So,
you should just choose a cheaper model for
yourself first.  So here, I'll choose
dipsit, okay guys?  Okay, please press
enter.  Then it will ask
you which terminal backend you want to choose;
just leave it as "keep current"
.  Press the enter key.  Here's
the interface where you can choose the
method you want to use to communicate with
this agent.  You
can connect via apps like Telegram,
WhatsApp, or Discord.
I'll choose
Telegram because it's
simple, lightweight, and free
.  Now press enter.
Next, here are the tools that
will be installed into your agent
.  Then you'll see that the
sections that are checked are the ones that have been selected for
you.  Here you can see
which tools you can use
for your agent.  For example,
here it will have features that are
not yet enabled.  These tools aren't
enabled here.  For example, let's analyze this video.
If you like this feature,
you can press the spacebar.  That's what it
will add up for you guys.  For example, here I
would choose to add what's called research, gathering
information from Twitter like
this.  I'll click this way.  There.
After you have selected the tools
you want here, please press
enter.  Next, it will ask
you to choose a provider here.
So, here we'll just choose
our local browser.
Our default browser is also
free like this.  Then I'll press
enter.
Then, it will ask you about the
providers that can handle
image creation or image editing
.  You can take your time installing it,
guys.  So here I'll
choose to skip this to let it go past this
.  Then, it will ask you
if you want to use any additional
tools or from any providers, and
you can choose from those options.
So, I want to skip this part; I can
install it later.  Please skip these parts
to save
time.  You can reread it and
decide whether or not you want to install it
.  Here, even if I skip the steps, the installation will still proceed
normally.  Then it will
ask you something here, just skip it.  Now
I'll press enter.  Then skip.
Okay, if it looks like this, then you've
successfully installed it.  There's
the text "setup complete" here.
Below, you'll find what are called
commands that you can use to run and
edit things.  Here, I've compiled
all those commands into a single
file like this, guys.  Everything is here
for you.  You
can just go here and type this command,
and it will handle that part for you
.  For example, earlier
we selected Telegram as the setting, but it
hasn't yet shown where we can enter
the tokens to connect to
Telegram.  So here, there
will be a command line that you should
type as I instructed: this is how to set up, this is
how to getway, guys.  Then I pressed
enter.  Then it will show the option to
choose where we can chat and
message our Hermit Agion
.  So here I'll select
my Telegram account again like this.
And please press the spacebar.
Press the spacebar to select.  Then
press enter.  The reason
I didn't set up Telegram in the
initial part of your instructions is because I
accidentally pressed the enter button.  To
set up Telegram, you need to
select Telegram.  You press the spacebar and
then press enter, just like
I did.  Then it will proceed to the step where
you set up Telegram.  For those of you who
are in the Telegram setup step,
remember to press the spacebar before
selecting.  Then, press enter
.  Then, it will lead to a step
like this: you need to
connect Telegram to
your Hion device.  Now, please go
to your Telegram app
.  Then, search for the
keyword "[clears throat] Bot Fer" here and
select the boss with the
green checkmark.  Then I'll
click start here.  Next, I'll select "
new bot" here to create a
new boss.  It will ask, "What would you like to name
this bot?"  I'll name it
Hermet agent bot.  Now press enter
.  Next, you should give
your bot a username.  And the
username must end with the word "boss,"
guys.  For example, here I would write that
this person is botting.  Then a
message like this will appear.  It will have a
token here.  Please click
on it.  When you click on it, it will automatically
copy your token.
Then you can come back here.  And here it asks
you which connection method you want to choose
?  So, here I
just chose the connection method, which is to find
this B Fer device.  So here I will
choose the second method, which is
option 2.  Enter this.  Then it will ask for
your telot token, which is the token code
you just copied.  Then I
'll pass it in like this.  Then I'll
press enter.  Then it will ask you where to enter the "
allow user ID" field.  This is the
permission for it to access your
boss's Telegram account
.  Then please go back to
my Telegram and
find the user named Infobot.   Please
choose the correct username
and logo.  Then
you click on it.  Then you click start
here.  Then a code will appear here for
you.  Please copy this for me.  Then
you come back here and paste that code,
then press enter again.  It will ask you whether you want to answer
yes or no.  So, my answer here
would be yes.  Then I pressed enter.  Okay,
so your Telegram account has
successfully connected to this device.
You'll see, and I have to
say it again, that it might look a bit like
programming, but in reality, it's
much simpler, right?
After you have successfully connected to
Telegram and completed
all the steps we've
outlined here, it should show "setup
complete."  Then
you have to enter a command.  So
here I'll type that and press enter.
So, what you're seeing here is a
compilation of the tools and
skills available.  And
here it includes 28 tools
and 68 skills.  So
these are the tools and skills
that it has installed on our character
.  We can install
more tools and skills later.  Now,
here we'll move on to the
gateway part.  In
general, it allows you to
send messages to your Telegram account
.  Now, I'll delete the things
that aren't here, okay?  Then
you guys typed me the word "tired".
Gateway install.  Then press enter.
Now, please wait a moment while it
processes this part.  After it has
responded like this,
I will now type another command
like this: `hermate gateway run`.
So, for some reason,
this app isn't working with
my Telegram chat yet, guys.  It says it
here.  From what you can see,
it looks a bit technical, right?
But the truth is, it's just text,
guys.  You'll read
here that it says it seems like
my Telegram username was misspelled
or something.  So now
all we need to do is re-enter this command, right?
So here, I'll just tell you to
type according to the instructions, okay?
Gateway.  That's the setup.  Now I'm going to
set up my Telegram again.
Okay, so my Telegram account has
been confirmed and successfully connected
here.  So here you'll
see that I didn't do anything at all
.  I'm just rewriting the sentence where
I getware setup here, and it has already checked
and successfully reconnected for me
.  So, I'm just having bad luck today, that's why
my Telegram is having problems
.  However, if
you follow the procedures I've
instructed you to follow correctly, it
will connect directly and successfully
.  Then, in this case
, let's say you find it too confusing, or you
've made a mistake somewhere and you're not sure what it is.
So, just come back here and type the
exact command again: "he, setup".
If you type this command correctly,
it will start the setup process from scratch
.  So, just repeat
each step one by one, and you'll be able to
access this step.
After it has successfully connected to
your Telegram account,
go back to Telegram and
click on the link of the bot
you just created here.
Please click on start here.  Usually,
the first question you ask wo
n't get a reply.  Or if it
gives an incorrect answer, for example,
just ignore it.  This
is normal.  Now, ask
a question to see if it answers
.  Let's see if it knows it's
her action or not.  And they will ask, "
Hello, who are you?"
It also revealed that Hion
here was developed in this way.  It
can help me do things like
this.  There, it knows who it is
now, guys.  Then I'll ask it
which model it's running on.
Okay, it also said that it ran
on Dipsit V4 Pro here from Operator, so that's
correct, guys.  Now I
'll give it some context.  The
purpose here is to let it know
where it is so that it can easily assist
me.  So I said that it's
running on a
Hostinger VBS like this inside an
aircraft.  And here, I also want it to show
me what
tools and skills it has.   Okay, so here's the
answer for you
guys.  I'll see.  Then it
also gave me this system information
.  This is the information
for my Hostinger VPS,
guys.  That's exactly the kind of post you'd find here.  CL
lists the tools and also the 68
skills here.  All the skills and
tools are listed here,
guys.  Next, I'll provide
them with the data and memory
.  Here, I'm trying to update
their memory so they
know who I am, what I do,
and what their names are, what they do,
and their roles.  So
here I'll put a simple sentence like
this.  Remember to save my name in your memory
.  My name is
Giang.  A YouTuber specializing in AI, mostly
for beginners and things like that.  And
you can describe
its role here.  You can
add names of things here.  Later, if
you want it to update the memory and store the
data, you just need to describe
what you want it to remember
.  Then, for the agent, you just
need to describe them.  You don't
need to turn anything on or off, configure anything, or
install anything.  All you
need to do is describe
what you want.  That
's the really great thing about those AIs
.  Okay, it updated
successfully.  This has been saved.  It has memorized
who it is and what it will do here
.  Now I'll give it a
task, and then I'll ask it to create
a skill for me.  If you
're familiar with skills, like the
abilities of AI creatures such as
claw or open claw, there
are many ways you can create
or build a skill.  For
example, there are ways you can
install a skill from
their library.  For example,
this one, or the open claw, has certain
skill calls.  You
can download whichever skill you want.  The second method,
which I really like and
frequently use,
is to ask it to do the work for
me.  Okay, I'll give it any t-shirt
.  Here, for example, I'll give
it a task: it has to research
trending topics on
YouTube, then put that
information into a file, and write an
output for me.  So, after
I give it a task like
this and after it completes it for me,
it will have a process, right?
And when I'm happy with
this result, I'll ask them to package
a skill or ability for me.  And
later, if I use it again, and I
request a similar job or task,
it will utilize
my skill again.  So here I
'll talk more about the skill section because
I find it interesting and I think
it's important.  And the third way
you can build a skill is to
request that it create a
skill from scratch.  So, you just need to
describe it like this: "I want you to create a
skill to handle and solve this problem for
this process
."  If you don't know, just
ask it directly: "How do I
create a skill for this process
?"  It will help you guys
.  And the fourth skill, and
also the strength of
this connection, is that it
will automatically build
skills that match your compositions as you work
.  Okay, here we'll do it the
second way, which we'll call taking the initiative
.  Okay, so here's the thing: when you give it
a request like this, it will
ask you for permission.  So,
you see these kinds of permissions here, so
please just allow them, guys.   Okay, so
let's just allow onsway here
.  Okay, so it's given me
the result here.  And it also
created two files like this for me.
So, the first file contains the data
I requested here.  And the second file
contains the three script outlines that I
requested.  And it also summarized the
things inside.  And here it will have
a really interesting part.  Here you will
find sales improvement reviews.
So, a YouTube research skill
has been created.  This means that it's based on
one of its previous jobs and it has
developed this kind of skill for itself
.  That's amazing, isn't it?
Then, in the case where you want to be
more proactive in developing
a skill within a process, let's
say you find the process
working well and you like the
results, then you can write a
sentence like this:  Save the
above process as a skill,
whatever you want to call it.  You can choose to name it or
not.  And from now on, whenever
I provide it with a topic,
for example, it will return
a similar result.  There.  Then we
'll start like this.  Okay.  So, it
has now created a skill
like this for itself, guys.  This is the name of
this skill.  What is this skill used for?
How to use these things.  Okay, I just need to
describe it like this and it will reuse
this skill.  But you don't need to
say much, or ask for a prom,
or any more detailed requests.  That
's fantastic, guys.  Now let's
move on to another example:
you can create a crunch-up, which means
you can create a work schedule
for your team.  For example,
it will start working for you every day at exactly 8:00 AM,
or maybe every week
.  For example, I've already
prepared a request like this:
you just need to describe it. Every
Monday at 8:00 AM, it has to
run a hot topic research skill and
find three topics about
something. Here, I'll also give you a demo
to show you that the
request to create something or run
a crunch job, a
scheduled task, is simply given a
request like this.   It's
very quick and very simple,
guys.  Here, it created a
schedule link for me and successfully created a crunchop
.  And if you want it tested immediately,
just write "test immediately".
It will run this whole thing again for
you right away so you can check
the results immediately.  And for those of
you interested in
adding more skill sets to your agents,
here's an
official website from a comprehensive agent platform that offers a
very diverse skill library from
leading reputable sources like Anthobit and Open Claw.
Hing Face, or Nvidia, as well as the
skills
developed by other communities and organizations here.
And
I'll also put the link to access this skill library
in the description of each video.
And once again, for safety reasons,
you should only install the skills of
the units with specific attributes here
.  Okay, now I'll talk a little
about the costs involved when
using this device, especially when
using it with tools
like Open Router, so you can track your
expenses.  Go back to the
Open Router tool and
go to the AB key section. There you
will see how much money your API key for the
ion device has used
.  And you can access
the activity section here.  This will
show an overview of what
you've used for which tool, as well
as the total span of requests
you've made.  Or
you can check this log section.  That
's the entry form.  That means
whichever model you've used will be shown
here.  It's
very well-organized and comprehensive here, guys.
Now we'll move on to another very
important step: converting the
model and choosing the appropriate model for
each tab.  And why
is this important to me? Because,
you know, there are currently
many items that are very powerful.  However,
because it's so powerful, it's also very
expensive, guys.  Therefore, you should only
use those powerful models for
tasks that are truly important.  For example, you'd only use powerful mods when
planning, setting goals, or making
deductions
.  As for tasks
like crawling websites and gathering
information, you should
use cheaper models.
Here, so you can check or
switch between these models, just
type in the code for this model.  This
will show the current model, which means
what the default model is and which provider you are using
.  Here I'm using
two providers:
MLE of Agent (here) and Open Router (
here).  I'll click on this "open router" button
.  Then, here at Open Router, there are
many models, you can view them
here and choose one.  Here
you can click "next" to
see more models
.  You can choose here.
Now we'll move on to the next step:
choosing which model to use for
which tasks is very simple;
you just need to specify your requirements.
The AIs up here are
really amazing again.  Then you write a
report like this for me.  So,
for tasks that run
weekly, or tasks that require
scheduling, or any other
important work, you should choose this model.
For messaging me or handling
routine tasks,
please choose this model.  You just need to
write a simple sentence like
that.  Then you will see that it is
updating the section containing the tasks
related to the enemy, and the memory
here has also been updated with the information for
us.  Which model should be used for this job,
and which model should be used for chatting with me
?  That's amazing, isn't it?
So here I'm sharing
the basics with you guys.  If
you want more details, you need to
describe it more clearly.  And honestly,
I had a high opinion of Hent, guys.  Compared
to the open claw, I find this one
simpler.  In other words, for those who prefer
simplicity and tasks that are
n't too complicated, you might
consider choosing this model.
For those who, I think,
are doing
typical office jobs, this image is a
reasonable choice.  And in the long run,
the longer you work with it, the
smarter it becomes, the better it understands you, and
therefore it will work faster because
it already has all the processes ready.
It will automatically package the skills, and
that will help
reduce your costs over time.
Okay then.  And once again, all the
links and commands
that I've compiled will be in the
description of the video.  And once
again, at Hostinger, you can register using
the link I've provided in the
video descriptions.  You will receive
this discount.  And remember to
enter the discount code "
Dong Giang fan" here to
get an additional 10% off!
And finally, on my YouTube channel,
Phan Dong Nhang, I also
share many tutorials and
examples about AI that you can
refer to here.  And on
my website fanong.com, I also
share free scientific resources, so
you can go there and
learn more.  And if you find
these videos helpful, please
give me a like!  And if
you want to see more content
from me and you don't want to miss
any of my other content,
please give me a subscription
here.